TEJASHWI RAJ

tejashwiraj211@gmail.com | Delhi, 110017

linkedin.com/in/tejashwi-raj-8a332a236

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm an English major and a hard-working college student. I have worked as a content writer intern and am an avid reader and writer. I believe I can fit the position of editorial intern perfectly because of my interest in books and articles.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Arts, *English Honors*, College Of Vocational Studies, Delhi University | 2021-2024 Minor: History

Senior Secondary School, ST. JOSEPH'S CONVENT HIGH SCHOOL, PATNA, BIHAR

Board - Indian School Certificate (ISC) | 2019 - 2021

Stream - Humanities, Percentage - 91

Higher Secondary School, ST. XAVIER'S HIGH SCHOOL,PATNA, BIHAR Board - The Indian Certificate of Secondary Education (ICSE) | 2009 - 2019 Percentage - 88

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Internship, Right Management India Private Limited | 12th July 2023 - 12 August 2023 Worked with the team leaders and helped them complete the entire project. Handled the project of Hyundai company and helped them audit their reviews. Learned skills like working in a group, Auditing, Ms.Excel.

Internship, The Socian | 1st December 2021 – 10th February 2022

Interned as a content writer.

Did thorough research, accumulated data, wrote articles, proofread and edited them. Worked on mini-series books.

Worked with the team and the team leaders, used and learnt skills like SEO,

WordPress, Copywriting and Proofreading.

Role, Tutored kids for 6 months | 2019

Helped them improve their grades and learn.

Learned skills like patience, communication skill, time management and responsibility.

Role, Worked on the editorial board of school and College | 2017

Wrote and edited manuscript worked in group and learnt organizational and collaboration Skill

Came up with new and innovative ideas to add to the magazine and worked to Implement them

SKILLS

Languages - English, Hindi, Basic computer skills, WordPress, Content Writing, SEO, Java at an introductory level, Proofreading, Copywriting, Microsoft Word, Excel, and Powerpoint.

VOLUNTEER AND COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Volunteer, Tarumitra Society | 2016, 2017, 2018

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Various articles have been published in two different books named "Pehchan" and "Book of 100 new quotes". Both the books are available on Amazon. Secured 19th rank on the state level and 169th rank on the international level in the International English Olympiad in 2019.

PORTFOLIO

Blog Link https://herhurricanes.home.blog/ PortfolioLink

https://docs.google.com/document/d/1aDU564dsrh2ROP2NfPzoCLZfottx3hO6XC1GVxkmDwo/edit?usp=sharing